myouterspace.com 2010-09-20

# Privacy Policy

Myouterspace.com Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting www.myouterspace.com (“Myouterspace”). Myouterspace is strongly committed to protecting your privacy. The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform our users about the information we collect and how and why we use that information. 

Disclosure Regarding Collection and Use of Personal Information

Myouterspace users can post information about themselves and access information about other users who have registered on the Myouterspace website. The website also gives users the ability to post other content such as photos, videos and other information. Myouterspace may continue to add additional features and functionality that are entertaining and useful for its users.

This Privacy Policy explains our online information collection and use practices and the choices you can make about the way we use and share such information. Please take the time to read and understand this policy so that you can understand how we use your personal information. 

IF YOU REGISTER ON THE MYOUTERSPACE WEBSITE, CREATE A PROFILE, POST INFORMATION, REQUEST INFORMATION, OR ENTER ANY CONTESTS OR PROMOTIONS THAT WE MAY OFFER, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS OUTLINED IN THIS POLICY. AS WE UPDATE AND EXPAND OUR SERVICES, THIS POLICY MAY CHANGE, SO YOU ARE ENCOURAGED TO REVIEW IT FROM TIME TO TIME.

The Information We Collect

Required Personal Information 

Each person who registers on the Myouterspace website is required to provide their email address. We require this information so that we can contact our users. In addition, all users are required to provide their first and last names, . We collect this information so that we can identify individuals, personalize our service and provide additional content tailored to our registered users. Finally, we require users to select a password to ensure that they are the only person who can control their personal information. You can view or change your information at any time by clicking on the Edit link on your main Profile page.

Optional Personal Information 

In addition to the required registration information, you may provide additional information about yourself or others, such as . You should be aware that Myouterspace does not review or confirm the accuracy of since this information is provided by users. Myouterspace allows you to post this information so that we can make it available to others who wish to learn more about you and to personalize the Myouterspace services. We also use this information to better understand our users. Providing this information enhances the Myouterspace service for both you and other users, but doing so is completely optional. 

Other Collected Information 

We may also collect certain non-personally identifiable information (generic information that does not identify you personally) when you visit any of our web pages including the following:  
Cookies Information: When you visit the Myouterspace website, we may send one or more cookies (a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters) to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. Myouterspace uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser. Persistent cookies may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. A session cookie is temporary and disappears after you close your browser. You can reset your web browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some features of the Myouterspace website may not function properly if the ability to accept cookies is disabled.  
Log File Information: When you use the Myouterspace website, our servers automatically record certain information that your web browser sends whenever you visit any website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser language, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform type, number of clicks, domain names, landing pages, pages viewed and the order of those pages, the amount of time spent on particular pages, the date and time of your request, and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.  
Clear GIFs Information: When you use the Myouterspace website, we may employ “clear GIFs” (also known as web beacons) which are used to track the online usage patterns of our users anonymously (that is, in a non-personally-identifiable manner). In addition, we may also use clear GIFs in HTML-based emails sent to our users to track which emails are opened by recipients.

How We Use Your Personal Information 

Please note that, except for your email address and password, any information that you provide to us or post on the Myouterspace website (in your Myouterspace profile, on discussion boards, in message areas or on other areas of the website) becomes publicly available and can be collected and used by others. Any of such information, including photos and videos may be redistributed through the internet and other media channels. Although you may limit public access to certain of your information (such as by using the My Privacy functionality on your profile page to restrict your profile to those Myouterspace users who are your friends), we recommend not posting any information that you may consider private, sensitive or that you do not want other people to know or to redistribute. Please see our safety tips page for more information. 

We will use the personal information you provide online to operate, maintain and provide the features and functionality of the Myouterspace website. For example, we may send you an email notification if you have won a contest. We may also send you an email offering products or services which we think you may be interested in. For example, we may send to you an email regarding special merchandise offers and announcements about products or services offered by us or an affiliated company. We may also contact you offline by sending you special offers, promotions and catalogs, which we think may be of interest to you. If you want us to stop using the personal information you provided in these ways, please email us.

We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally-identifiable information (such as anonymous user usage data, cookies, IP addresses, browser type, clickstream data, etc.) to improve the quality and design of the Myouterspace website and to create new features, functionality, promotions and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing user preferences and trends.

We may use cookies, clear gifs, and log file information to: (a) remember information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the Myouterspace website; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in promotions, sweepstakes, and contests.

Updating or Removing Your Personal Information 

You may update or remove from your Myouterspace profile any information you post at any time. Complete removal of certain information (such as your name, e-mail address or password) requires terminating your user registration. We provide links to manage your information on your Myouterspace profile page. To view your profile page, click on the “My Profile” link on the navigation bar on the left side of any Myouterspace page.

How We Share Your Personal Information 

We will not share your email address or password except (a) if it is for the purpose(s) you provided it; (b) with your consent; (c) as may be required by law or as we think necessary to protect our company or others from injury (e.g. in response to a court order or subpoena, in response to a law enforcement agency request or when we believe that someone is causing (or about to cause) injury to or interference with the rights or property of another); (d) with other persons or entities with whom we contract to carry out internal site operations or our business activities (for example, sending out a product or a promotional item that you have requested); or (e) notifying you when we make changes to one of our terms of service, this policy or other user agreements.   
Use and Disclosure of Non-Personally Identifiable Information   
We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to analyze how our site is used, improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your user experience. We may also share this information with third parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions or functionality on the Myouterspace website.

Email Choice/Opt-out 

We will send periodic updates on Myouterspace to our registered users that may include updates on new functionality and the announcement of contest winners. Users who no longer wish to receive our email updates or other email notifications may opt-out of receiving these communications by terminating their registration.  
Collection of Information by Others 

The Myouterspace website may contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different from ours. Please be aware that Myouterspace is not responsible for the privacy practices of any other website. We encourage all users of the Myouterspace website to be aware of when they leave our website, and to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Myouterspace through the Myouterspace website.

We may offer email services, contests, sweepstakes, or promotions that are sponsored by or co-sponsored with non-affiliated companies. Based on our agreement with them, these third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that site visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the contest, sweepstakes, or promotion. We have no control over the use of this information by these companies.

We also use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit the Myouterspace website. The third-party advertising technology that we use on our site uses information derived from your visits to this site to target advertising within this site. In addition, our advertisers may use other third-party advertising technology to target advertising on this site and other sites. In the course of advertisements being served to you, a unique third-party cookie or cookies may be placed your browser. In addition, we may use Web beacons, provided by third-party advertising companies, to help manage and optimize our online advertising. Web beacons enable us to recognize a browser’s cookie when a browser visits this site, and to learn which banner ads bring users to the Myouterspace website. To “opt-out,” please [click here](http://www.doubleclick.com/us/corporate/privacy). <http://www.networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp>

Forums, Message Boards, Newsgroups and Community Tools 

From time to time we may make forums, message boards, newsgroups and other community tools available to you. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information for other users to view and for us to use. For example, from time to time, we may use the content you write (including your name) for promotional purposes, in email newsletters or elsewhere. By using Myouterspace and/or these forums, message boards, news groups, and other community tools, you agree that we may do so. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information in these areas, since anyone - not just us - may use publicly posted information.  
Our Commitment to Security 

We believe we have in place the appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security and correctly use the information we collect online as well as offline. Whenever personal information is passed on to non-affiliated companies, to the extent practical, we require that they also have in place the appropriate safeguards. We cannot, however, guarantee that they do so.

International Users 

If you are visiting Myouterspace from a location outside of the United States, your connection will be through and to servers located in the United States and all information you provide will be processed and maintained in our web servers and internal systems located within the United States. By using Myouterspace, you authorize the export of personal information to the U.S. and its storage and use as specified above when you provide such information to us. 

Applicable Law and Jurisdiction

This policy and our legal obligations are subject to the laws of the and the United States of America, regardless of the location of any user. Any claims or complaints must be filed in the .

Special Note for Parents 

If you have concerns about the Myouterspace Website or its services, please email us. Our site will not knowingly accept personal information from anyone under 18 years old in violation of applicable laws. If you believe that your child under 18 has gained access to our site without your permission, please email us. We have taken commercially reasonable steps to restrict use of this site to those who are at least 18 years old. We do not sell products for purchase by children and all children’s products we sell are for purchase by adults only, or with adult permission.

Change of Ownership

In the event of a change in ownership, or a direct merger or acquisition with another entity, we reserve the right to transfer all of Myouterspace’s user information, including names, and email addresses, to a separate entity. All registered users will be notified of any change in ownership, merger or acquisition of Myouterspace’s assets by a third party, and may choose to modify any of their registration information at that time.

Changes to this Policy 

Because our business needs may change over time, we reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions from this policy at any time. If at any time in the future we plan to use your personally identifiable information in a way that differs from this policy, we will revise this policy as appropriate. Your continued use of Myouterspace following the posting of any changes to this policy means you accept such changes. This policy is effective .

How to Contact Us 

If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy policy you may email us or write to the following address:

Myouterspace

Attn: Privacy

Telephone:   
Facsimile:
